<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Aun&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Aun&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 15:26:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aunfl0w.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML 5 routes &amp; deep links with apache</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2019/html5routesapache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 15:26:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2019/html5routesapache/</guid>
      <description>HTML5 client routing Deep links to client side applications using frameworks that make use of HTML5 routing, such as Angular, can be problematic. The web browser client side application utilizes regular URL paths for client side application navigation that appear in the browser address to be locations of actual resources. This however is not the case, the running application in the browser makes use of javascript pushstate to navigate to states within the client side application and does not request the resource shown in the browser address bar when running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking Observability</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2019/netcommands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 21:52:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2019/netcommands/</guid>
      <description>Notes on networking observability commnads For many years and many UNIXen the netstat command has been the way to get information on the current state of TCP/IP and UNIX sockets. The recent man pages for netstat on linux state that netstat is &amp;ldquo;mostly obsolete&amp;rdquo; and use ss instead. The man page for ss, &amp;ldquo;another utility to investigate sockets&amp;rdquo;, says that is allows showing information similar to netstat. Some notes on using ss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Thinking</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/functional/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:58:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/functional/</guid>
      <description>Functional Thinking For functional programming.
A Non Functional Aproach This is a sample program that processes a generated sample list of data. With the list of data it performs common operations such as find items, count types, sum things up etc. Do you see the duplicate code that is copy pasted with small changes? Can you tell what each loop is doing without thinking about what is going on in the loop or using the comments?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing Frozen Particle Waves</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/freedomtoadd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 12:04:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/freedomtoadd/</guid>
      <description>Growing Frozen Particle Waves I recently added docker support to Frozen Particle Waves. If you are looking for an OSS project where you can contribute to this is a great option. It isn&#39;t finished so you have a great base to contribute updates and exhibit your skills.
Some additions and updates that you can help with:  Add a storage system and services to add users and cameras. Separate the UI into a more up to date framework such as Angular.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Slaughterhouse</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/process-slaughterhouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/process-slaughterhouse/</guid>
      <description>Cattle not pets If you are running a stateless scale out application the cattle not pets mantra will be stuck in your thoughts. Sick processes and whole container environments that misbehave are taken out back of the server and executed. For the benefit of those handling on call support and for immediate recovery the easy button is great. However, it ignores the real problem. If you had a leaky roof the long term solution is not get more buckets to catch the water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not the view I was expecting</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/not-the-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 22:57:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/not-the-view/</guid>
      <description>Not the view I was expecting It was a wonderful clear labor day on the river. The water was cool and flowing east just west of the Lake Wylie dam. A break from floating on a tube to climb a tree to a rope swing ends early with a fall. A gash to the calf and a splash in the water. In short time my daughter will be whisked away in an ambulance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Frozen Particle Waves</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 20:13:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/start/</guid>
      <description>Frozen Particle Waves Frozen Particle Waves is a project I started to learn and demonstrate the use of a Spring Boot server app with an Angular client side UI. Currently it can be used to aggregate images from webcams that expose images through http endpoints and also supports basic auth. It uses Spring Boot as the application server to provide REST endpoints to the client side Angular UI. Spring security is used to secure the endpoints and handle user authn/authz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary Scaling X</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/scale-linux-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 22:47:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/scale-linux-x/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m a bargain hunter. Lately I have been playing with some low powered windows cloudbooks. I picked it up &amp;ldquo;refurbished&amp;rdquo;, the box and packaging looked new, for less than $200. It has a full HD 14&amp;rdquo; screen which I was searching for as the similar size 720p model I had before was a little on the pixeley side for text. Also, it was repurposed as a computer for a student. As usual I made a backup image of the internal storage for when it gets passed on to the next person that wants windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XOR NOT Security</title>
      <link>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/not-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:13:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aunfl0w.github.io/2018/not-security/</guid>
      <description>We used xor to keep your secrets safe If you experience this situation it is time to look closer. While XOR will make a string that is eyeball safe it isn&#39;t going to provide protection from even the casually interested. Weather this was chosen by the developers due to timeline pressures and added to the fix it later list or just an unfortunate set of google results you need to understand why simple XOR isn&#39;t an option for security.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>